http://www.promat-ap.com/en/privacy-policy

Privacy Notice
This Privacy Notice (“Notice”) as describes. Promat International (Asia Pacific) Ltd. is referred to as “we”, “us”, “our” or “ours”. Website visitors or a person who is using and accessing this Website (or via www.promat.com.au, www.promat.com.hk, www.promat.com.my, www.promat.com.sg), the Content or the Services is referred to as the “User”, “you” or “yours”.
Acknowledgement and Consent
By communicating with us, using our enquirer or subscription services, download our resources, email or others engagement, you acknowledge and consent for us to collecting or processing of your Personal Data by us as described in this Notice.
Any substantial changes on terms of this Notice made may/not be announced/notified, please keep visit this page regularly for further updates/amend of this Notice. We shall remain the right on how we maintaining data privacy and user confidentiality details we collected and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Please cease the use of this Website if you are disagree or not accept with any of the practices described in this Notice or do not consent to our collect, use, disclose, store and/or give access of your Personal Data as described in this Notice.
Collection of Personal Data
In our continuous efforts to serve you better, is important for you to understand what personal data we collect, how we collect it, and why it’s necessary.
We collect “Personal Data” relating to you, from which you are identifiable, including but not limited to your name, email address, telephone number, mobile number, your occupation, your designation in your company, your company details, the industry field in which you work in, which geographic regions you are from, personal interests, any information about you which you have provided to us through:
subscription form, registration forms, enquiry forms, contact forms or any other similar forms/emails;
partner websites, social media platforms’ pages includes LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Instagram, Pinterest., if you subscribe, follow, like or are a fan of such pages;
telephone log information when you call us, such as your telephone/mobile number;
requested reference materials;
marketing activities, events and exhibitions booth;
conduction of workshop, seminar, presentation and products demo; and
personal data may be directly collected from an individual (F2F).
We may request additional information from you to help us verify you and/or to help us respond to your request if necessary.
Your personal data may also be collected from cookies used on the Websites to help us understand your surfing behavior through browsing activity on the Websites.
These cookies can remember your browser and user's computer but do not personally identify users, and do not pass any information outside of Promat International (Asia Pacific) Ltd.
Use of Personal Data
The main reason we collect your Personal Data is to ensure you get the best service possible. To contact you or your company and to inform about our latest updates of products or services which we believe may be interest to you.
We may combine your Personal Data we have obtained about you and process the Personal Data for business, marketing and administrative purposes of Promat International (Asia Pacific) Ltd. which shall include, without limitation the following:
to respond to your registration, subscription, enquiry of our products and services;
to provide you with any of our services or products you have requested;
to process your requests for reference materials and distribute to;
to process your participation in selected events, exhibitions, surveys, promotions organised by Promat or our joint partners;
to understand and analyse our products and services as well as your needs and preferences;
to develop, enhance, improve and provide our products and services to meet your needs;
to send you emailers or other marketing information of our selection of brands/products/systems, our affiliates and/or joint partners with whom We are conducting promotions or programs in which you may be interested through email/mail/text messaging (SMS);
to send you newsletters, festive greetings from us or from our joint partners;
to make this Website available to you and the content is user friendly and accessible for you;
to acknowledge your consent, to contact you by email/mail/text messaging (SMS) with products and services which we think may interest you;
We may not use your Personal Data for new purposes which are as yet unforeseen in this Privacy Notice except on the basis of an applicable statutory permission. In any event, prior to using Personal Data for other purposes, We will inform you about such change to this Privacy Notice. In case of consent-based activities, We will not process your Personal Data for such new purposes without first obtaining your consent.
Sharing of Personal Data and Transfer of Personal Data to Third Parties
We will not make your Personal Data available to any third party and shall not publicly disclose the Personal Data unless such transfers are based on your specific consent, necessary for the performance of a contract entered into between you and Us, or when such transfer of Personal Data is otherwise authorised or compulsory by law or by order of an administration or judicial authority.
In certain circumstances, We may transfer your Personal Data to the following recipients:
Within our organisation's offices;
Our authorised Branding dealers;
Our joint partners, e.g. certified installer by requests;
Please note that your Personal Data may also be shared within our organisation's in connection to others Promat division.
Withdraw or revoke consent
Please notify us in writing if you wish to withdraw or revoke your consent from our use and process your Personal Data for the Purposes and the Additional Purpose as stipulated herein.
If you wish to unsubscribe to the processing of your Personal Data for Additional Purposes by us, please click on the link “Unsubscribe” which is embedded in the relevant email in order not to receive any email in the future.
Data Protection Compliance Officer
Etex’s group Compliance Officer can be contacted at complianceofficer@etexgroup.com with regard to all issues related to processing of your Personal Data and to the exercise of your rights under the applicable national and European legislation relating to data protection.
Governing Law and Dispute Settlement
All such entities are governed by this Privacy Policy and are bound by appropriate confidentiality and data transfer agreements and shall
have exclusive jurisdiction in any dispute being determined under the law.
For further information in this respect Personal Data Protection act and on the said legislation, please refer to the respective law:
Malaysia - Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) 2010
Singapore - Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (PDPA)
Hong Kong - Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap. 486 of the Laws of Hong Kong)
Australia - Privacy Act 1988 (Privacy Act)
Effective Date of Privacy Policy
This Privacy Notice was effect since 1st January 2019. Last updated in 23rd May 2019.
Unit 19-02-01, Level 2, Wisma Tune,
No. 19, Lorong Dungun, Damansara Heights,
50490 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.
